You know, for a first take, I think it
went pretty well. We had things moving
in real time, calling back to our main
hub system, actively reporting on our
mobile device. It was uh it was pretty
good. Uh and here we're seeing sort of a
take two. We're going up a level. uh
we're adding a device into the ecosystem
basically trying to see in what way
shape or form can we communicate or uh
add extra communication uh to our talks
by having a simple watch device which
everybody's using. So uh today we're not
only taking a look at the nature of
privacy 3D printing curation and control
uh but we're also taking a stab at our
own demo of uh open source technology.
So, couldn't think of a better place to
talk to people about what they think,
what motivates them, what got them to
stand up, uh, but also test some stuff
out, see what people think. So, uh,
let's check it out. All right. So, today